gr8people.com 2015-07-23

# Privacy Policy - gr8 People, llc - Collaborative Recruiting Platform

* * *

gr8 People has received TRUSTe's Privacy Seal signifying that this privacy statement and our practices have been reviewed for compliance with the TRUSTe program viewable on the validation page available by clicking the TRUSTe seal. The TRUSTe program does not cover information that may be collected through downloadable software. The TRUSTe certification covers our collection, use and disclosure of information we collect through our website http://gr8people.com/ and our service platform https://apps.gr8people.com. The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service for which the Client has engaged gr8 People.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact TRUSTe at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.

gr8 People complies with the U.S.-E.U. Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal data from the European Union member countries. gr8 People has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view gr8 People’s certification, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/

gr8 People collects information under the direction of its Clients, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. If you are an applicant of one of our Clients and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Clients that use our service, please contact the Client that you interact with directly. We may transfer personal information to companies that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are covered by the service agreements with our Clients.

gr8 People has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the gr8 People’s Client (the data controller). If the Client requests gr8 People to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 days.

We will retain personal data we process on behalf of our Clients for as long as needed to provide services to our Client. gr8 People will retain and use this personal information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

We collect the following personal information from you

  * Contact Information such as name, email address, mailing address, phone number
  * Unique Identifiers such as user name and password

We also collect the following information from you

  * Information about your business such as company name, company size, business type
  * Demographic information such as education and zip code

The information provided to gr8 People through the Site is used by gr8 People for marketing or employment purposes. Before we use it, however, we offer you the opportununity to choose whether or not to have your information used in this way. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

gr8 People provides informational content through the Site and generally does not use the Site for the sole purpose of collecting personal information from visitors. gr8 People may use the data it collects for internal purposes: solving technical issues, calculating usage statistics, marketing, product development, employment and general informational improvement.

gr8 People will not disclose to third parties any personal information, except to the extent necessary as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, brankruptcy proceedings, or similar legal process. When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

In the event of a transfer of ownership of gr8 People, such as acquisition by or merger with another company, gr8 People will provide notice via email and or/a prominent notice on our Website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have before any personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, ask to have it removed from our testimonial on our site or deactivate it by making the change on our careers page or by emailing our Customer Support at support@gr8people.com or by contacting us by telephone at the contact information listed below.We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving our newsletter or marketing emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails, accessing the email preferences in your account settings page or you can contact us at support@gr8people.com

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by gr8 People and our marketing partners, affiliates, or analytics or customer support service providers. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies for authentication and to remember users’ settings (e.g. language preference). Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. 

We may combine this automatically collected log information with other information we collect about you. We do this to improve services we offer you, to improve marketing, analytics, and site functionality.

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by clicking here (or if located in the European Union click here) Please note this does not opt you out of being served ads. You will continue to receive generic ads.

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. gr8 People stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at support@gr8people.com to request that we remove this information from our database.

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as a Social Security Number) and when you login to our platform, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

gr8 People utilizes industry standard security measures to ensure the security of all data both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission through the Internet. or method of elctronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at support@gr8people.com

gr8 People restricts access to your personal information to employees who need to know that information to operate, develop or improve our products and services. Please note, however, that gr8 People cannot guarantee the confidentiality of any communication or material transmitted to/from gr8 People via the Site or e-mail. gr8 People is not responsible for any interception or interruption of any communications through the Internet or for changes to or losses of data.

Users of our Sites are responsible for maintaining the security of any password, user name, or other form of authentication involved in obtaining access to password protected or secure areas of any gr8 People site(s). In order to protect you and your data, gr8 People may suspend your use of a site, without notice, pending an investigation, if any breach of security is suspected. Access to and use of password protected and/or secure area of any gr8 People site is restricted to authorized users only. Unauthorized access to such areas is prohibited and may lead to criminal prosecution.

gr8 People may include or offer third party products or services on our website. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites and encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

gr8 People may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practies, we will post those changes on this page. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

Visitors to our Site may at any time opt out of having their personal information used by gr8 People by contacting gr8 People, llc via e-mail or postal mail at the address below.

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://www.g8people.com

400 South Main Street  
New Hope, Pennsylvania 18938  
USA  
privacy@gr8people.com

Publish Date: 5.28.2015
